Rodolfo Portillo III

13031 Park Crossing Apt. 2304, San Antonio, Texas 78217

(915) 240-4687

rudy@rportillo.com

https://rportillo.com

Service Desk technician with experience in several areas of product support which include manual software testing, test case creation, defect triage, and reporting of tests executed and defects uncovered. This experience is supplemented with in-depth, day-to-day customer support of the AFPIMS system.

Areas of experience include:

JIRA/Confluence	 Implementation of web APIs 	 JavaScript
 Creating and maintaining test cases/scripts 	HTML 5	 Excellent verbal and written communication
• Python	• CSS 3	
-		
Certifications		

Security+ CE

CompTIA, June 2019 Expires: June 2022

ITIL V4 Foundation

AXELOS, September 2020

Expires: N/A

Secret Security Clearance

Department of Defense, September 2020

Expires: N/A

Work Experience

Service Desk Analyst, Gryphon Technologies; San Antonio, Texas

May 2019 - Present (1 Year, 6 Months)

- Provide support for basic incident resolution and requests reported to the Service desk.
- Assist customers through phone calls, emails and ticket tracking system.

 Resolve issues by completing initial assessment, triage, research, and resolution of basic incidents and requests regarding the use of application software products and infrastructure components.

Line Cook, Alamo Drafthouse Cinemas; Austin, Texas

February 2017 - May 2019 (2 Years, 3 Months)

- Responsible for the training of new-hires in various areas of a professional kitchen
- Follow corporate recipes for food preparation with a major focus on accuracy and minimal waste
- Responsible for maintaining consistent execution of entrees in a fast-paced, high-pressure environment
- Adhere to all state health compliance requirements

Field Tech II, Texas Gas Service; Austin, Texas

November 2013 – December 2016 (3 Years, 1 Month)

- Part of a team responsible for maintaining the integrity of the natural gas infrastructure for Austin, TX
- Held and maintained several government-required qualifications pertaining to natural gas
- Developed strong teamwork and dynamic problem-solving skills in a hazardous environment

Education

Wester Governors University (WGU Texas); Austin, Texas

July 2020 - Present

Major: B.S. Information Security and Assurance

GPA: 3.5

Anticipated Graduation: January 2022

Austin Community College; Austin Texas

December 2016 - May 2019

Major: A.S. Information Security and Assurance

GPA: 2.75

University of Texas at El Paso; El Paso, Texas

August 2008 - May 2012

Major: B.S. Computer Science

GPA: 2.5